novaworlds.com 2013-08-05

# Nova Worlds - Homepage

**Foreword  
**We at DAO Games consider your right to privacy to be of paramount significanceand this is our privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, store and use your personally identifiable information. By “personally identifiable information” we mean information that would allow someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your full name, postal address, telephone number, email address or credit card information. However, it does not include aggregated information that, by itself, does not permit the identification of individual persons, like statistics about how many users visited our website during a given timeframe, how long they stayed, or what browsers were used. 

DAO Games has taken the necessary technical and organizational precautions to ensure that the regulations for data privacy are respected both internally as well as by external service providers.Your personal data is protected against unauthorized access and loss through the use of various electronic,technical, physical, administrative and contractual measures.  
This Privacy Policy applies to all DAO Games websites, products and services, including:

  * 

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By registering for an account on DAO Games Websites and/or using our products and services, you accept the Privacy Policy in full. If you do not accept the policy, or any part, please do not register for an account or use our products and services. By registering, you accept that you have both read and accepted the Privacy Policy. 

DAO Games reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Should the policy be changed, a notice will be posted on our homepage and other related locations. We will treat your continued use of our websites as acceptance of these changes from their effective date as shown above.

If you have any question about this privacy policy, or think DAO Games is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact us by e-mail at [support@novaworlds.com](mailto:support@mechanist.co). Please do not continue to use our websites until you are satisfied and can accept this policy in its entirety.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information  
**DAO Games collects personally identifiable information when you: 

  * register to use our website, products and/or services; 
  * complete questionnaires; 
  * register for contests or giveaways; 
  * order products and services from us; 
  * subscribe to our newsletters or take part in our promotions, marketing surveys and email campaigns;
  * request for customer support and/or other technical services; and
  * otherwise use our services where personal information is required.

Also, if you access our Products through an integrated and approved Third Party then you are allowing us access to certain information from that Third Party. The information you allow us to access may vary per our Product and across different Third Party platforms and is affected by the privacy settings you have on your computer or internet device and the choices you make with that Third Party.

**Other Information Collected and Stored**  
In addition to login information, we will automatically collect certain non-personal information about your use of our websites, products and services. This includes:

  * IP addresses including time and date 
  * Cookies, local flash data 
  * Statistical information such as the browser type, operating system, redirecting URL, date, time, page used, total time of use, frequency of use, etc. 

The above-mentioned non-personal information will remain anonymous unless you provide us with personal information or have provided such information in the past. For instance, if you’ve created an account, your account information (including name, email address and billing and shipping information) may be linked to the items you purchased at our cash shop (i.e., purchase order history).

**Who Collects the Personal and Non-personal Information**  
DAO Games Ltd., which owns and operates the NovaWorlds.com and DAOGames.me websites as well as the products City of Steam and The Lost Titan, is the company that collects the listed information on our sites. Our mailing address is Office 405, 4th Floor, JBC1 Building, Jumeira Lake Towers, Dubai, UAE. Our customer service email address is [support@novaworlds.com](mailto:support@mechanist.co).

**How the Personally Identifiable Information is Used**  
Personally identifiable information which we collect for a particular purpose will only be saved and used for that purpose, unless you have agreed to allow us to use it for some other purpose, as described in this Privacy Policy.

For the purpose of handling payments, DAO Games has the right to disclose user data to service providers instructed to collect the user fee insofar as this is necessary for the calculation of the fee and for settlement with the user. Furthermore, weare entitled to provide user data to third parties to whom receivables due to us from the user have been assigned provided that this is necessary to collect the receivables. We shall inform the user of the names of such third parties. If we cooperate with third parties in order to provide its services, we shall oblige such parties to comply with applicable data protection laws and to ensure adequate data protection. 

We may also use the information provided by or stored on the user purely for internal checks as regards demography, user interests and user behavior. This use is carried out anonymously. We may also statistically evaluate information on the user in an anonymous and aggregated form for advertising and market research. If and as far as we use user data to create user profiles, we shall never pass on such profiles without the prior consent of the user and shall immediately stop such utilization of user profiles if the user at some point objects to such use of his data. 

Although we regard your right to privacy of paramount importance, due to legal rules beyond our control, we cannot fully guarantee that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be forced to disclose your information to law enforcement or other appropriate third parties in connection with criminal investigations, investigation of fraud, infringement of intellectual property rights, or other suspected illegal activities, or as otherwise may be required by applicable law, or, as we deem necessary in our sole discretion, in order to protect the legitimate legal and business interests of DAO Games.

**Privacy Protections for Children**  
In order to protect the privacy interests of younger Internet users, we do not allow children under the age of 18 to use our services without the consent of their parents or legal guardians. We also provide a number of provisions regarding the personally identifiable information (PII) of children. These are that a parent/guardian has the right to review the information the site has collected from their child, have their child’s PII deleted from the site and also request us to stop collecting further PII from their child in the future.

To request removal of your child’s information, please send us an email (to the address below) and be sure to include in your message the same user name, password, and email address that your child submitted. If your child has used your credit card on our websites without your permission, contact us immediately at [support@novaworlds.com](mailto:support@mechanist.co).

**Security**  
If you visit any chat room or put messages on a bulletin board you should be aware that you are disclosing information to anyone who might happen to be in the chat room or visiting the bulletin board. This means that others can get hold of any information that you give in these areas and you may get messages from people who you don't know.

You are responsible for your information on the Internet. Make sure that you are careful when you visit our site in a public place like an Internet cafe. DAO Games can only be responsible for your information when it is received on our own computers and not whilst it is in any intermediate environment.

**Third Parties & Advertisers**  
Generally we do not give your information to other third parties unless you let us. However, given that we partner with a number of external payment service provider companies to enable you to make payment via a wide range of payment options, we share your billing information with such companies insofar as is necessary for the processing of your payment or to prevent or detect fraud. 

We never disclose information to advertisers. What we do is show you the advertisements of advertisers you might be most interested in bearing in mind what we know about you from your registration information. We do not give any information to advertiser themselves so they will never know about you personally.

We do give advertisers information where you are not identified, such as how many people have clicked on their advertisements, what age range those people are and whether they are male or female. This may also include information about their particular interests; however they will never know who these people are.
